RAYMOND ORTIZ

An Auto Insurance Claims Adjuster with five years of professional experience specializing in customer service, loss valuation, and damage assessments. A proven track record of performing inspections on damaged vehicles and supporting customers throughout the claims process.

123 Bedford Avenue, New York, NY, 12345 ray mon dortiz@examp I e.co m (123) 456-7890

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

AUTO INSURANCE CLAIMS ADJUSTER

Allstate, New York, NY November 2019 - Present

AUTO INSURANCE CLAIMS ADJUSTER

Nationwide Insurance, New York, NY May 2017 - November 2019

- Deliver high-quality service to customers to assess vehicle repair needs, damages, and compensation, communicate with empathy and understanding throughout the claims process and achieve customer satisfaction scores of 92% annually
- Perform physical inspections of vehicle damages, create estimates and valuations, and conduct negotiations for settlements totaling S5K-S15OK
- Serve as liaison between customers, auto repair companies, and Allstate to review insurance claims, repair costs, and adjustments
- Executed inspections on damaged vehicles for auto insurance claims, performed loss valuations, and gathered eye-witness accounts to determine liability
- Coordinated cross-functionally with customer service and legal teams to ensure appropriate compensation and settlements based on damages

EDUCATION

Associate of Science (A.S,) Auto Repair Technology

University of Syracuse, New York, NY Septem be r 2015 - May 2017

KEY SKILLS

- Customer Service
- ♦ Auto Insurance Claims Processing
- ♦ Policy Interpretation
- Claims Analysis
- Property Valuation

CERTIFICATIONS

Insurance Claims Adjuster License,
State of New York, License
#12345678